This one is the older sister.
This one is the younger sister.
Incorrect.
This one is the older sister.
This one is the younger sister.
General, what do you think?
Even Cui Hu cannot
tell them apart this time.
This is a sure win.
Two brides,
and they look exactly the same.
General,
Ke'ying wants to marry in my place.
But I still want to ask,
can you keep her safe, General?
As long as Ke'ying is willing to marry me,
what's done is done.
No one will dare say a word.
I will explain it to His Majesty myself.
You know, General,
Ke'ying has always had feelings for you.
But as her older sister,
I must ask one more thing.
Will you treat her
with true sincerity, General?
If you only want to use her
for your own gain,
please be merciful
and let my younger sister go.
My words carry little weight,
so naturally, I cannot sway
your decision.
But my father knows
you plan to use this marriage
to control the Duke's Estate.
If I were the one married off,
he naturally wouldn't say much.
But Ke'ying
is his most favored one.
He will definitely not let this go.
What are you guys talking about?
You look so serious.
I was telling your sister
that from the very beginning,
you are the only one
I truly want to marry.
As for your sister,
just let her and Chu Qingyun
be together.
Does this count
as a straightforward confession?
He's serious.
Mr. Chu, you're here.
Then you can talk with Wan.
We won't bother you.
Let's go. Let's go.
I heard Ning Yuanci
asked the Emperor to marry Xue Keying.
Is it true?
And it seems
they are in love
with each.
By the way, you came at the right time.
I have something to ask you.
I don't plan
to restore my mother's painting
of Nirvana of Phoenix.
I want to ask you
to copy a new one for me.
With the engagement resolved,
Xue Ruowan is a free woman.
It's only a matter of time before
the male and female leads' relationship
gets on track.
What are you thinking about?
You look so happy.
I was wondering
when Ruowan and Mr. Chu
will finally fall for each other.
Aren't you happy
to become the General's wife?
In the Duke's estate,
I was the beloved
and carefree Second Lady.
Not to mention that marrying you
comes with the risk of being beheaded,
and I'll have to
manage such a huge General's estate
in the future.
Plus, there are so many people out there
who want to kill you.
I'd be living in fear every day.
Tell me,
what exactly are the benefits
of being the General's wife?
I can promise you,
that as long as you are by my side,
I will never let you
get hurt.
What is this?
A betrothal gift prepared
exclusively for you.
Is this pure gold?
I've gotten married
no less than 10 times in costume dramas,
and played a substitute bride five times.
But this is the first time
someone has proposed to me like this.
You said before
that kissing you
requires your permission.
So,
are you willing?
I...
I a-
I am...
Aren't you afraid I'm lying to you?
And I'll just stab you
on our wedding night?
Do you think I can't tell
when you're acting
and when you're not?
You can insult my character,
but you can't insult my acting skills.
I have awards to prove it.
Then tell me,
am I being sincere
or fake right now?
You have so many secrets.
How would I know?
See?
I was right.
Are you hiding some
unspeakable scandal?
Do you want to know?
I will tell you
when you marry me.
I will uncover it sooner or later.
General, the poisonous herb
you asked me to investigate
is indeed only found
in the Northern Frontier.
Just as I expected.
You went to such great lengths
to ask His Majesty for this marriage
just to get close to Xue Shiyan,
to make it easier to find
evidence of his treason.
As for who you marry,
isn't it all the same?
Why defy the imperial decree
and agree to
Xue Keying's substitution scheme?
Ever since I was engaged to Xue Ruowan,
she has been repeatedly attacked.
All signs point to framing me.
Xue Shiyan would not hesitate to
sacrifice his own daughter's life
to clear his suspicion of treason.
Such a ruthless man,
I do not believe
he would show mercy to Xue Keying.
It is better to bring her
to my side sooner.
It is
safer this way.
In the Battle of Black Water River
five years ago,
someone leaked military intelligence,
causing the tragic deaths
of the old Marquis and his wife.
So far, we have only found out
that the secret signal
used by the Northern spies
is a deer totem.
But this totem
has never appeared in the Duke's estate.
Could Xue Shiyan
be colluding with foreign enemies
in another way?
Have you caught the man
from the lantern festival?
I have sent men to search for him,
but he has not been found yet.
You mentioned before
that this man
was carrying a
highly suspicious bag.
He hides so well,
he is definitely not an ordinary person.
Find him even if you
have to dig three feet under.
I've learned a bit from My Lady
over the years.
Though not as good as Mr. Chu,
it shouldn't be worse
than the Second Lady's.
My Lady will definitely like it
when she sees it.
Lan,
Lan!
Stop hitting her!
What did she do wrong?
Beat her!
No!
Father, I was wrong.
It's all my fault.
Please don't hit Lan anymore.
Stop hitting her!
Stop!
Drag My Lady away.
Keep beating her.
Lan!
Lan! My Lady!
My Lady!
My Lady, Lan,
let's go.
Keep beating her!
Lan!
Why are you hitting her?
No, no!
Why? Why on earth?
She confessed to poisoning you,
hiding my paintings,
and stealing jewelry from the storehouse.
Unforgivable.
Impossible.
Whether it is true or not,
you can ask her yourself.
My Lady,
I am sorry.
I did it all for your own good.
But I didn't expect...
Stop!
Now you believe it, don't you?
Beat her!
Xiaolan!
Beat her to death! Xiaolan!
Stop!
Get out of here alive.
No!
Stay alive.
Xiaolan!
What bad luck.
Take her away.
Mother!
They said...
Lan was beaten to death last night.
Is that true?
Yes.
We finally found
the one who poisoned that loser.
Our names are
finally cleared.
Are you saying
Lan was the one
who poisoned Xue Ruowan?
How is that possible?
Why wouldn't it be?
She confessed it herself
before she died.
She even tried to frame you before.
Now,
she finally got what she deserved.
Where is Xue Ruowan?
I need to find Xue Ruowan
and see how she is.
Stop
right there!
Why are you stopping me?
Keep a close eye on the Second Lady.